MANISH TOMAR

Bootstrap5

jQuery

Node.js

API

• Express.js

• Git | GitHub

WEB DEVELOPER

https://personalsitef5cs.onrender.com

https://github.com/manish tomarr1

tomarrmanish@gmail.com

+91 8476889763

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Well-qualified Web Developer. Six months of virtual experience and familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities.

SKILLS

- C++
- JavaScript
- Data Structures
- Algorithms
- React.js
- HTML5
- 11111120
- CSS3

EDUCATION

- MASTERS IN COMPUTER APPLICATIONS
 MMMUT Gorakhpur | 2021 - 2023
 8.3/10 GPA
- BACHELORS IN COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

DIMS Meerut | 2017-2020 66.5%

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT END SOFTWARE ENGINEERING VIRTUAL EXPERIENCE

SKYSCANNER | SEPTEMBER 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

- HTMT5 | CSS3 | Bootstrap | JavaScript | jQuery | API
- Create Front End Web Apps

POWER
PROGRAMMER
VIRTUAL
EXPERIENCE

INFOSYS | JUNE 2022 - SEPTEMBETR 2022

- Algorithmic Thinking | Problem-Solving | Code Debugging | Advanced Data Structures
- Software Development Methodologies: Waterfall
- and Agile | Software Architecture

PROJECTS

EXPENSE TRACKER

- This Web Application allows users to track and preserve their own expense information. Users also filter the expenses by years.
- Technology Used : React.js.
- https://expensetrackerbymanish.netlify.app/

PERSONAL SITE

- The personal site contains fundamental information about me, including my skills, work experience, projects, etc.
- Technology Used: HTML5, CSS3, Bootctrap5, JavaScript, Express.js.
- https://personalsitef5cs.onrender.com

CERTIFICATION

- Power Programmer Virtual Experience | Infosys
- Front end software engineering virtual experience | Skyscanner
- Front End Development | Udemy